const questions = [
	{
		question: 'Who is the author of the One Piece manga?',
		suggestions: ['Masashi Kishimoto', 'Tite Kubo', 'Eiichiro Oda', 'Akira Toriyama'],
		correctAnswer: 2,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of Luffy's first crewmate?",
		suggestions: ['Sanji', 'Usopp', 'Zoro', 'Nami'],
		correctAnswer: 2,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which Devil Fruit did Luffy originally eat?',
		suggestions: ['Mera Mera no Mi', 'Gomu Gomu no Mi', 'Hito Hito no Mi', 'Yami Yami no Mi'],
		correctAnswer: 1,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Who was the captain of the Whitebeard Pirates?',
		suggestions: ['Kaido', 'Big Mom', 'Shanks', 'Edward Newgate'],
		correctAnswer: 3,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the name of the sea where the Straw Hat Pirates start their journey?',
		suggestions: ['Grand Line', 'East Blue', 'Calm Belt', 'New World'],
		correctAnswer: 1,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: "What is the real identity of the 'Gomu Gomu no Mi' revealed in the Wano arc?",
		suggestions: [
			'Mythical Zoan: Sun God Nika',
			'Paramecia: Rubber Rubber Fruit',
			'Logia: Lightning Fruit',
			'Mythical Zoan: Monkey God',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the ancient weapon that Robin is searching for through Poneglyphs?',
		suggestions: ['Poseidon', 'Pluton', 'Uranus', 'All of the above'],
		correctAnswer: 3,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which of these characters is a member of CP0?',
		suggestions: ['Kaku', 'Rob Lucci', 'Blueno', 'All of the above'],
		correctAnswer: 3,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is Joy Boy in One Piece lore?',
		suggestions: [
			'A legendary pirate from the past',
			'A title given to the Pirate King',
			'An ancient figure linked to Laugh Tale and the Void Century',
			'A warrior from Elbaf',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2,
		point: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which island is known as the final destination of the Grand Line?',
		suggestions: [
			'Fish-Man Island',
			'Sabaody Archipelago',
			'Raftel (Laugh Tale)',
			'Enies Lobby',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2,
		point: 10,
	},
];

export default questions;
